You
All right, damn it wanna go again
Are you cheating what? Oh, you sure about that? Oh, please here. Watch me do it
My lucky day, sorry, you've got to be cheating
Yeah, now put up her shut up. Just take it. You'll get me next time for sure
Okay
I can't with this guy
What's with you you've been heaving sighs like that since we left the capital
Uh
Sorry about that
So what brings you this far up north
With all due respect, why do you care the northern territories are dangerous and though you're traveling solo?
You don't exactly strike me as the adventuring type major not you are still a kid, right? Hey, sorry
But there's no reason I need to answer any of your questions
Okay, what's your freaking deal kid? She's trying to be nice
No, Sarah, it's not like she's just like fight. He's just a little blunt. I know but you've been worried about him since yesterday
Suzanne, and now he's acting like you're harassing him or something
Search and rescue. My mother was a victim of the mass teleportation in Fatoa
Hmm
Yeah, well, whatever
Still don't have to be so friendly
What's your plan the northern territories are huge you're not gonna find her stumbling around I
Suppose you're right one step at a time. I guess do you have a lead I?
I
Could give you a quick primer on the Northlands while we're on the road if you like
Yeah
Well if you're offering sure
All right now pick the wax out of your ears and listen up kiddo
You may have noticed most countries in the Northlands are poor but the three great magical nations all do pretty well for themselves
The kingdom of Rinoa is known for the University of Magic the Duchy of Nerys produces great magical implements and the Duchy of Bacharant
Specializes in arcane research. We're actually on our way to Bacharant now
Anyway, those three pulled their knowledge and formed an alliance and now they're the dominant power in this region with me so far
I
Hey the gangs all here. I'm beat let's get going already
It's freezing here
Excuse me
I'd like a room for a month
Ah, you got it just a second
I'll need your signature
Great you'll be on the third floor far end of the hall that's for pay
You're not traveling to get over Eris
You're here to find Zenith
I hear the pay is great though
Oh, yeah?
Whoa, it's a little kid
Must be a newbie
Yeah, right
Oh, he's just playing make-ball
Who's this little girl?
What's he doing here alone?
Looks like a pushover to me
Excuse me
Excuse me, huh?
Would you mind helping me officially disband my party?
Oh, sure
Sir, I, um...
Sorry
Here
This will only take a moment
Oh, man
Do you think...
Yeah, sounds like his party got wiped out
I can't imagine what that's like
Being the sole survivor
I'd like to take this job
Huh?
Oh, but what about your party?
I'll do it alone
Huh?
But this is an A rank job
Doing it yourself would be...
I'll be harping and just give me the details already
What's up?
Arguing about something?
I wouldn't call it an argument, no
Sure, sure
Didn't mean to eavesdrop, but I did
Your old party was wiped out
But you need money to look for your mom
That's why you want to take this job by yourself, right?
W-well...
Doesn't look to me like you're up for it, though
Kinda looks like you don't even care whether you live or die anymore
So, that being said
How about this?
Why don't we take it on together?
Huh?
I don't know
We don't usually go for outside help, but we're all on unfamiliar turf right now
So at least until we get our bearings here
Couldn't hurt to team up
No, thank you
I'd rather work alone
There's only so much you can do by yourself
The one thing you need above all is help, kid
And if you ask me, the best way to get it is by joining parties and staying alive
Tell them I'm right, you guys
Mm-hmm
You agree, don't you, Sarah?
Yeah, sure
So that's it
Of course she doesn't want my help
She just pities me
Now you do look pretty young still
But I'll bet you can hold your own
What are your specialties?
I'm good at supporting melee fighters with magic
Usually stick to the rear
Do you?
Perfect
We were just talking about how our party could use someone else on the back line
Okay, then
I'll go
Great, that settles it
So let's spend the rest of today getting ready
And plan to meet at the North Gate tomorrow morning
We can work out whatever the updated formation will be on the road
Sounds good
Oh my gosh, are you still sulking?
You are such a big baby
Will you shut up already?
Even more like her than I thought
Okay, let's go
Yeah
This should be a pretty good payday
Yeah?
Let's get it over with and have a drink
Haven't you had enough yet?
Just got my hands on some awesome wine
Congratulations
Now focus on the job
Please
I've got this
That could take on the seven great powers right now
Check this out
Boom
Flicks
Hey, you're early
You didn't seem too excited yesterday, so I wondered
I just happened to wake up early
Uh-huh
My name's Rudeus Greyrat
I'm a mage
And I can cast spells without incantations
Rudeus
Good to have you
Oh
My name's Suzanne.
I'm one of our frontline fighters, and Counter Arrow's illustrious sub-leader.
Sub-leader? You're not the one in charge?
Nah, I keep everyone on the same page, but I don't give the orders.
Right, that would be me. I'm Timothy, long-range magic attacker, and despite all outward appearances, the actual party leader.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Amir. I'm the party's main healer.
The name's Patrice. I fight up front with Suzanne, obviously.
Go on. Your turn.
My name's Sarah. I'm a mid-range archer.
And just so we're clear, I don't want you here at all, and I never did, okay?
I'm only putting up with you because it was Suzanne's decision.
So if you screw it up and get someone killed, I'll make you regret it.
Okay.
Give it a rest, Sarah.
But...
Look, someday we might go our separate ways, and you might have to join a new party full of strangers.
Wait, what? Are we gonna disband?
It's a possibility.
You could afford to be picky about your teammates back in Asura, but that's not gonna fly from here on out.
So you'd better learn to work with people other than us.
Oh, so it wasn't just pity. I'm also a teachable moment.
We're going to wait for the sun to set before going after those luster grizzlies.
Sound good?
Well, because they don't see too well in the dark. Is that why?
Ah. Hmm. Exactly.
And since you brought it up, let's review our strategy.
First, as soon as we spot the enemy, Rudeus will stall on the outskirts, and Timothy will...
Thin the herd with magical attacks while they charge.
Patrice and I will handle the ones that manage to close the distance, work out the rhythm in the moment.
And Sarah will...
Back you up.
And if one of us gets hurt fighting up close, then...
I'll be right there to heal you.
Simple and clean. You got all that, Rudeus?
Yeah, but...
What is it?
I don't think I'll have much to do. Should I shift to mid-range support once you two engage?
No, you don't have any idea how the fighters move yet.
Then after I delay them, I could help Timothy thin their number groups...
Everyone knows you need to conserve mana in a drawn-out fight.
Stick to stalling them. That's all we need from you.
Okay. But if needed, I could join in at close range.
Do you want me to shoot you in the back?
You're not actually a member of this party you know, so shut up and do as you're told.
Right.
She really is just like her.
Sarah, don't make things uncomfortable right before we get to work.
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
What?
Sarah's attitude. She's not a bad kid, but she's getting a bit full of herself.
The last silent caster I knew was a teacher back in my school days.
You must be quite a mage to pull off that technique.
For all the good it's done me. Not like that skill's gonna bring my family back.
What have we got, Sarah?
About 20, all sleeping.
Do you think we can take him out?
Oh yeah, duh. Don't you?
Good. Let's get started then.
Let the great protection of fire converge where thou seekest.
Oh raging inferno, deliver us a blazing bounty.
Exa-flame.
Let the great protection of fire converge with thou seekest.
Oh raging inferno, deliver us a blazing bounty.
Exa-flame.
Let the great protection of fire converge where thou seekest.
Wow, piece of cake.
At this rate we won't need to get up close and personal at all.
Let the great protection of fire converge with thou seekest.
Oh raging inferno, deliver us a blazing bounty.
Exa-flame.
Let the great protection of fire converge with thou seekest.
Oh raging inferno, deliver us a blazing bounty.
Exa-flame.
What the? Are those black grizzlies?
It's mud. They're covered in mud.
Hey, Timothy!
Retreat! Retreat!
Retreat!
Too late. We're dead.
Unless...
No.
Forget it. I'm sick of this.
I've already lost everything anyway.
I can keep them busy! You guys run right now!
No! I'll stay too!
You won't even slow them down!
Damn! We're surrounded!
They're too much for one person.
If you stay, we all stay.
He's right. Let's do it then!
Let this divine power be rich in nourishing, offering those whose strength has been lost the strength to rise again!
Healing!
They're staring death in the face, but they won't run.
Why?
Why is my heart pounding so hard?
Why am I breathing so heavily?
And why do I find this so... exciting?
Right. Of course.
I remember now. There's a reason people stay on their ground.
I can't believe I ever forgot it.
What are you doing?
Leave this to me. I'll be okay.
I'll be okay.
No!
I don't know.
Guess we owe you one.
If it hadn't been for your help, we'd all be dead.
I'm just glad you agreed to bring me along.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go home.
Yeah.
Thanks for the save.
I do owe you one.
Great.
It's the outsiders.
I bet they think they're hot shit.
That was barely even a real job.
Yeah, I wish they'd get lost already.
My party and I are celebrating our first successful job here tonight.
So next round's on us, everybody.
Listen up, you guys.
We may be new here, but you better remember our names, all right?
We are Counter Arrow and Rudeus.
Rudeus, Rudeus, Rudeus, Rudeus.
Rudeus, Rudeus, Rudeus, Rudeus, Rudeus.
Ow, my neck.
I'd completely forgotten to get serious about living.
What the hell is wrong with me?
Of course you haven't lost everything, you moron!
Remember when you first came into this world?
Remember Roxy?
Remember the day she took you outside?
She taught you so much.
And you can't betray those lessons now.
I haven't lost everything.
Not by a long shot.
Sure, I lost something that I cared about very much.
But that doesn't mean I have nothing left to live for.
I have all of them.
I can't fall to pieces.
We may be far apart, but I'm not alone.
And things still suck.
But I've got to remember, I've had it way worse.
I'll keep moving forward, and I'll do what needs to be done.
Master, please guide me.
Master, please.
However, heart's honest and don't know...
So, do you want your best to joinstep?
But, thank you for watching.
I've had anotherố thinks,
Oh, dieserasily,
That's all I did.
He fades away.
My life was BEHINDED,
Heads along the rocks,
and getting dirty.
That's respuesta, I've had to be helped me.
Learn smarter, Thomas,
T usual,
In the day,
that's all about everything.